<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Paimon\'s Tavern</string>
    <string name="welcome">Step inside the bustling tavern, weary traveler, where the scent of adventure fills the air and laughter mingles with the echoes of epic tales. Raise a glass to the mysteries of Teyvat, for within these walls, you\'re among comrades who share your passion for Genshin Impact. Welcome, and may your journey through this wondrous world be ever thrilling!</string>
    <string name="overview">Paimon is the Mascot of a Popular Anime Style Open World Game Called Genshin Impact. It is a story of twin sibling calling themselves as a Traveler, Traveling on different kinds of the Universe. \n\n After Travelling across Teyvat and finally decides to leave the universe, their path was blocked by the Unknown God, Capturing Both two of them and thrown away.\n\n His twin sister Lumine was awakened first, and never been seen anymore. \n\n After 500 Years, Aether(Lumine\'s Twin Brother) finally woken up and their powers gone, he travels the unknown horizon and do some fishing, instead of fish He capture some Unknown Creature, calling herself Paimon. \n\n Paimon was Drowning and losing hope but thanks to the traveler, her life was saved. So as a Token of Appreciation, Paimon decides to be the Traveler\'s Best Guide Companion to help him search for her lost Sister. \n\n They traveled several nations together, Fight and Struggle, on the latest chapter of the game they Already on the 5th Nation of Teyvat\'s 7 Nations meeting the nation\'s Archon to find some answers for her lost sister. \n\n Paimon was Also known for her Talkative Personality, and Passion for Tasty and Yummy food that Traveler always treats her. \n\n Paimon was very thankful to the Traveler for all of the good things happened, and as a token of Friendship, she decide to Build the Paimon\'s Travern so that they can eat as much as they like, and earn money in the Process.</string>
    <string name="order_text">There is atleast 5 different kinds of Menus that represents the 5 Nation\'s Specialty. To Choose a Menu click the image. There is a tons of Items to choose from feel free to explore the app. \n\n
        to Add Quantity Click Plus and Subtract Click Minus, the Qnt will indicate the total quantity you ordered note that the maximum amount you can order is 10 per item . Click the Order Button to add to the list and Click Clear if you want to remove all, click proceed to finally review the receipt,\n\n
        Take note that all of items You Order are Correct and make it\'s your final decision before continuing. After Clicking Order Button, this means all of the list you ordered are final, if you misclick something or you are planning to change your mind, Click the Cancel Button and the list you\'ve ordered will be delete. \n\n Click Order Again, if you want to continue using the app.</string>

</resources>